David Stick Papers PC.5001
State Archives of North Carolina
- Organizations and Agencies, 1930-2009 and undated; 45072; Stick, David, 1919-2009
  - Outer Banks Community Foundation (OBCF), 1979-2009; 6697; Stick, David, 1919-2009
    - Council on Foundations, 1980-1986; 6855; Stick, David, 1919-2009
      - Correspondence, 1984; 27118; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Correspondence)
      - Correspondence, 1985-1986; 27119; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Correspondence)
      - Miscellaneous Publications, 1984-1985; 27120; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous Publications)
      - Newsletter vols. 1-3, 1983-1984; 27121; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Newsletter vols. 1-3)
      - Newsletter vol. 4, 1985; 27122; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Newsletter vol. 4)
      - Newsletter vol. 5, 1986; 27123; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Newsletter vol. 5)
      - Special Reports, 1980-1984; 27124; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Special Reports)
      - Washington Update, 1986; 27125; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Washington Update)
    - Current, 1983-2003; 27126; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Current)
    - Donations, 1983-1989; 27127; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Donations)
    - Executive Director, 1986; 27128; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Executive Director)
    - Expenses - David Stick, 1982-1986; 27129; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Expenses - David Stick)
    - Financial Statements, 1982-1986; 27130; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Financial Statements)
    - Frank Stick Fund, 1989-1994; 27131; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Frank Stick Fund)
    - Gifts and Bequests Brochure, 1992; 27132; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Gifts and Bequests Brochure)
    - Grants, 1983-2009 (bulk 1983-1986); 6856; Stick, David, 1919-2009
      - Grants and Disaster Guidelines, 2009; 27133; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Grants and Disaster Guidelines)
      - Application Forms, circa 1984; 27134; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Application Forms)
      - Applications, 1985-1986; 27135; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Applications)
      - Avon Methodist Parsonage, 1986; 27136; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Avon Methodist Parsonage)
      - Cape Hatteras School, 1984; 27137; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Cape Hatteras School)
      - Cape Hatteras School P.T.A., 1985; 27138; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Cape Hatteras School P.T.A.)
      - Chicamacomico Historical Association, 1984; 27139; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Chicamacomico Historical Association)
      - College of the Albemarle, 1986; 27140; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder College of the Albemarle)
      - Correspondence, etc., 1985-1986; 27141; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Correspondence, etc.)
      - Criteria, 1983; 27142; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Criteria)
      - Dare County Library, 1984; 27143; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Dare County Library)
      - Dare County Social Services, 1984; 27144; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Dare County Social Services)
      - Dare County Tourist Bureau, 1986; 27145; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Dare County Tourist Bureau)
      - Dare VAC, 1986; 27146; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Dare VAC)
      - Future Possibilities, 1983-1986; 27147; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Future Possibilities)
      - Girl Scouts, 1983; 27148; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Girl Scouts)
      - Green Thumb Program, 1984; 27149; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Green Thumb Program)
      - History of Grants, 1992; 27150; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder History of Grants)
      - Kitty Hawk Elementary School, 1985; 27151; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Kitty Hawk Elementary School)
      - Manteo High School, 1985; 27152; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Manteo High School)
      - Marine Resources Center, 1984; 27153; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Marine Resources Center)
      - Miscellaneous, 1989-1992; 27154; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous)
      - Nags Head Woods, 1983; 27155; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Nags Head Woods)
      - Nags Head Woods, 1986; 27156; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Nags Head Woods)
      - North Banks Rotary Club, 1984; 27157; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder North Banks Rotary Club)
      - North Carolina State University Recreation Department, 1984; 27158; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder North Carolina State University Recreation Department)
      - Outer Banks Hotline, 1984; 27159; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Outer Banks Hotline)
      - Outer Banks Hotline, 1983; 27160; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Outer Banks Hotline)
      - Policy and Procedures, 1985; 27161; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Policy and Procedures)
      - Rejected, 1985-1986; 27162; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Rejected)
      - Roanoke Island Historical Association, 1985; 27163; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Roanoke Island Historical Association)
      - Summaries, 1983-1985; 27164; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Summaries)
      - Volunteer Groups, 1984-1986; 27165; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Volunteer Groups)
    - Hurricane Isabel Fundraising etc., 2003-2004; 27166; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Hurricane Isabel Fundraising etc.)
    - Insurance, 1983-1986; 27167; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Insurance)
    - Internal Revenue Service and NC Department of Revenue, 1983-1985; 27168; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Internal Revenue Service and NC Department of Revenue)
    - Ledger, 1982-1986; 27169; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Ledger)
    - "Looking Ahead", 1985; 27170; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder "Looking Ahead")
    - Loose/Miscellaneous, 1998-2007; 27171; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Loose/Miscellaneous)
    - Meetings, 1982-1987; 6857; Stick, David, 1919-2009
      - Breakfast Meeting, 9 February 1983; 27172; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Breakfast Meeting)
      - Annual Meeting, 26 October 1983; 27173; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Annual Meeting)
      - Annual Meeting, 30 October 1984; 27174; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Annual Meeting)
      - Annual Meeting, 30 October 1985; 27175; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Annual Meeting)
      - Annual Meeting, 23 October 1986; 27176; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Annual Meeting)
      - Meetings: Board of Directors, 1982-1987; 27177; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Meetings: Board of Directors)
      - Organizational Meetings, 1982; 27178; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Organizational Meetings)
    - Member Binder: David Stick, 1993-1994; 27179; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Member Binder: David Stick)
    - Membership, 1982-1991; 6858; Stick, David, 1919-2009
      - Applications and Contact Cards, 1985-1986; 27180; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Applications and Contact Cards)
      - Correspondence, 1982; 27181; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Correspondence)
      - Correspondence, 1983; 27182; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Correspondence)
      - Correspondence, 1984; 27183; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Correspondence)
      - Correspondence, 1985; 27184; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Correspondence)
      - Correspondence, 1986; 27185; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Correspondence)
      - Charter Member Drive, 1982-1983; 27186; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Charter Member Drive)
      - Patron Drive, 1983-1984; 27187; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Patron Drive)
      - Membership Drive, 1984-1985; 27188; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Membership Drive)
      - Membership Drives, 1982-1991; 27189; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Membership Drives)
      - Membership Drive, 1985-1986; 27190; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Membership Drive)
      - Membership Drive, 1986-1987; 27191; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Membership Drive)
      - Member Lists, 1984-1985; 27192; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Member Lists)
      - Member Lists, 1985-1986; 27193; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Member Lists)
      - Member Lists, 1986-1987; 27194; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Member Lists)
      - Member Lists, 1986-1989; 27195; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Member Lists)
      - Member Lists, 1990; 27196; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Member Lists)
      - Membership Year - Proposed Change, 1985; 27197; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Membership Year - Proposed Change)
      - Prospective Members, 1982-1983; 27198; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Prospective Members)
    - Memorial Funds, 1982-1986; 6859; Stick, David, 1919-2009
      - Austin, Inez D., 1983; 27199; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Austin, Inez D.)
      - Brown, Aycock, 1984; 27200; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Brown, Aycock)
      - Daniels, M.L., 1982-1983; 27201; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Daniels, M.L.)
      - Fearing, M.K. Sr., 1983; 27202; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Fearing, M.K. Sr.)
      - Meekins, D.V., 1985; 27203; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Meekins, D.V.)
      - Miscellaneous, 1982-1986; 27204; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous)
      - Neighbors, George, 1985-1986; 27205; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Neighbors, George)
      - Owens, R.V., 1983; 27206; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Owens, R.V.)
      - Prospects, 1983-1984; 27207; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Prospects)
      - Stick, Frank, 1983-1984; 27208; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Stick, Frank)
    - Meritorious Award, 1996; 27209; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Meritorious Award)
    - Meritorious Award Scrapbook, 1996; 27210; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Meritorious Award Scrapbook)
    - Minutes and Correspondence, 1991-1992; 27211; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Minutes and Correspondence)
    - Minutes and Finances, 1986-1990; 27212; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Minutes and Finances)
    - Miscellaneous, 1982-1986; 27213; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous)
    - Miscellaneous, 1983-1990; 27214; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous)
    - Miscellaneous Files, 1990s; 27215; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous Files)
    - Miscellaneous Notes, 1983-1986; 27216; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous Notes)
    - Nature Conservancy - Fundraising, circa 1980s; 27217; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Nature Conservancy - Fundraising)
    - Newspaper Advertisement, 31 November 1985; 27218; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Newspaper Advertisement)
    - North Carolina Community Foundation, 1997-1998; 27219; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder North Carolina Community Foundation)
    - Oakes, Bob, 2005; 27220; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Oakes, Bob)
    - Operating Procedures, 1986; 27221; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Operating Procedures)
    - Personal, 1990s; 27222; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Personal)
    - Printing, 1982-1983; 27223; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Printing)
    - Printing, 1984-1985; 27224; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Printing)
    - Progress Report, 17 June 1982; 27225; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Progress Report)
    - Publicity, 1982-1983; 27226; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Publicity)
    - Publicity - Clippings, 1982-1990; 27227; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Publicity - Clippings)
    - Publicity and Promotion, 1990s; 27228; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Publicity and Promotion)
    - Publicity and Reports, 1993-1998; 27229; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Publicity and Reports)
    - Reports: Annual and Semiannual, 1983-1986; 27230; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Reports: Annual and Semiannual)
    - Reports, etc., 1982-1989; 27231; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Reports, etc.)
    - Reports, etc., 1990-1991; 27232; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Reports, etc.)
    - Reports, Minutes, and Correspondence, 1991-1994; 27233; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Reports, Minutes, and Correspondence)
    - Scholarships, 1984-1985; 27234; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Scholarships)
    - Scholarships, 2003-2005; 27235; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Scholarships)
    - Shoreline Typing, 1985; 27236; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Shoreline Typing)
    - Unmet Needs Study, 1983-1986; 6860; Stick, David, 1919-2009
      - Foundation News, 1983-1986; 27237; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Foundation News)
      - Final Report, 1983; 27238; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Final Report)
      - Questionnaires: Churches, 1983; 27239; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Questionnaires: Churches)
      - Questionnaires: Individuals, 1983; 27240; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Questionnaires: Individuals)
      - Questionnaires: Organizations, 1983; 27241; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Questionnaires: Organizations)
      - Questionnaires: Miscellaneous, 1983; 27242; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Questionnaires: Miscellaneous)
      - Steering Committee Correspondence: Burrus, Jay, 1983; 27243; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Steering Committee Correspondence: Burrus, Jay)
      - Steering Committee Correspondence: Bortz, Nelson, 1983; 27244; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Steering Committee Correspondence: Bortz, Nelson)
      - Steering Committee Correspondence: Dare County Health Department, 1983; 27245; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Steering Committee Correspondence: Dare County Health Department)
      - Steering Committee Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1983; 27246; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Steering Committee Correspondence: Miscellaneous)
      - Steering Committee Meetings, 1983; 27247; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Steering Committee Meetings)
  - Outer Banks History Center (OBHC), 1978-2008; 6698; Stick, David, 1919-2009
    In the course of his career as an historian and author, David Stick amassed a large library of monographs, serial publications, maps, manuscripts, photographs, and other North Caroliniana. In the mid-1980s, Stick decided to donate his personal library to the State of North Carolina, with the stipulation that a facility would be established in Dare County to make the materials available to the public. The agreement was formalized in 1986, and the Outer Banks History Center opened to the public in 1989. The facility serves as the eastern unit of the State Archives of North Carolina and continues to collect materials related to the North Carolina coast. The Outer Banks History Center (OBHC) subseries contains materials primarily dating from the first decade of the OBHC's operations, as well as material predating the State Archives' acquisition of the collection. Included are card catalogs, indices, shelf lists, and other early inventories of the David Stick library; files related to the OBHC's affiliate groups (the OBHC Associates and the OBHC Advisory Committee), papers from the dedication of the facility on 7 May 1989, records related to major acquisitions (such as the Edwin Graves Champney Drawings and Aycock Brown Photographs); appraisal records; and two narratives written by David Stick about the OBHC: "My Personal Papers in the Outer Banks History Center" and "How the David Stick Library Became the Outer Banks History Center."
    - Acquisitions Policy, 1992; 27248; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Acquisitions Policy)
    - Advisory Committee, 1988-1991; 27249; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Advisory Committee)
    - Advisory Committee, 1992; 27250; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Advisory Committee)
    - Advisory Committee, 1995-2000; 27251; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Advisory Committee)
    - Associates, 1990-1994; 27252; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Associates)
    - Associates, 1995; 27253; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Associates)
    - Associates, 2001; 27254; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Associates)
    - Associates, 2001-2004; 27255; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Associates)
    - Aycock Brown Photographs, 1984-1991; 27256; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Aycock Brown Photographs)
    - Background, 1985-1996; 27257; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Background)
    - Budgets, 1986-1989; 27258; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Budgets)
    - Card Catalogs: Map Shelflist Cards, circa 1987; 27259; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Card Catalogs: Map Shelflist Cards)
    - Card Catalogs: Unidentified Card Catalog [folders 1-3 of 5], circa 1980s; 27260; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Card Catalogs: Unidentified Card Catalog [folders 1-3 of 5])
    - Card Catalogs: Unidentified Card Catalog [folders 4-5 of 5], circa 1980s; 27261; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Card Catalogs: Unidentified Card Catalog [folders 4-5 of 5])
    - Card Catalogs: Want List [3 folders], 1970s; 27262; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Card Catalogs: Want List [3 folders])
    - Champney Drawings, 1990-1991; 27263; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Champney Drawings)
    - Clippings, 1997; 27264; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Clippings)
    - Coastal History Service Center, circa 1989; 27265; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Coastal History Service Center)
    - Correspondence, 1987; 27266; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Correspondence)
    - Dedication, 7 May 1989; 27267; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Dedication)
    - Dedication Speech, Clippings, 1989-2008; 27268; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Dedication Speech, Clippings)
    - Dough, Wynne C., 1989-1994; 27269; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Dough, Wynne C.)
    - EII (Elizabeth II) Engines, 1987-1989; 27270; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder EII (Elizabeth II) Engines)
    - Exhibits and Programs, 1991-1994; 27271; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Exhibits and Programs)
    - Frank Stick Trust, 1987-1988; 27272; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Frank Stick Trust)
    - Graveyard of the Atlantic Museum, 1988-1990; 27273; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Graveyard of the Atlantic Museum)
    - How the David Stick Library Became the Outer Banks History Center, 1989; 27274; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder How the David Stick Library Became the Outer Banks History Center)
    - Ice Plant Island Plans, 1991-1994; 27275; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Ice Plant Island Plans)
    - Items on Loan, 1992-1994; 27276; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Items on Loan)
    - Job Specifications, 1987-1993; 35195; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Job Specifications)
    - Library, 1978-1993; 6901; Stick, David, 1919-2009
      - Alexander, Christine, 1986; 27277; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Alexander, Christine)
      - Appraisal, 1980; 27278; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Appraisal)
      - Appraisal: Books, 1986; 27279; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Appraisal: Books)
      - Appraisal: Maps, 1986; 27280; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Appraisal: Maps)
      - Appraisal, 1990; 27281; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Appraisal)
      - Appraisal, 1993; 27282; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Appraisal)
      - Archives and History Staff, 1986; 27283; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Archives and History Staff)
      - Architects, 1986; 27284; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Architects)
      - Background Material, 1978-1985; 27285; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Background Material)
      - Basnight, Marc, 1985-1986; 27286; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Basnight, Marc)
      - Brown, Aycock: Heirs, 1985; 27287; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Brown, Aycock: Heirs)
      - Cashion, Jerry C., 1983; 27288; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Cashion, Jerry C.)
      - Clippings, 1986-1987; 27289; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Clippings)
      - Computer HICATS Codes, 1986; 27290; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Computer HICATS Codes)
      - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1979-1986; 27291; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Correspondence, Miscellaneous)
      - Cultural Resources Department, 1980s; 27292; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Cultural Resources Department)
      - Description of Contents, 1985; 27293; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Description of Contents)
      - Donation Agreement (Cultural Resources), 1986; 27294; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Donation Agreement (Cultural Resources))
      - Dorsey, Patric, 1985; 27295; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Dorsey, Patric)
      - Hodgkins, Sara W., 1983-1984; 27296; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Hodgkins, Sara W.)
      - Inventory, 1980; 27297; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Inventory)
      - Inventory, Revised, 1985; 27298; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Inventory, Revised)
      - Legal, 1985-1986; 27299; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Legal)
      - Miscellaneous, 1986; 27300; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous)
      - Miscellaneous Notes, circa 1980s; 27301; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous Notes)
      - Misenheimer, Larry, 1986; 27302; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Misenheimer, Larry)
      - Legislative Acts, 1985-1986; 27303; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Legislative Acts)
      - McKay, David N., 1982-1985; 27304; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder McKay, David N.)
      - National Park Service, 1978-1982; 27305; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder National Park Service)
      - Price, William S., Jr., 1984-1986; 27306; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Price, William S., Jr.)
      - Stack Layouts, Stick Home, circa 1986; 29320; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Stack Layouts, Stick Home)
      - Taxes, 1985-1986; 27307; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Taxes)
    - Maritime History Conference, 1992-1994; 27308; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Maritime History Conference)
    - Maritime History Council, 1994-1995; 27309; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Maritime History Council)
    - Miscellaneous, 1989-1995; 27310; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous)
    - Miscellaneous, 2001-2008; 27311; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1987-1993; 27312; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous Correspondence)
    - Miscellaneous Gifts, 1990-1991; 27313; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous Gifts)
    - Miscellaneous Logs and Reports, 1990; 27314; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous Logs and Reports)
    - Miscellaneous Notes, 1987-1994; 27315; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous Notes)
    - Misenheimer, Larry, 1987-1993; 27316; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Misenheimer, Larry)
    - My Personal Papers in the Outer Banks History Center [2 folders], circa 2000; 27317; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder My Personal Papers in the Outer Banks History Center [2 folders])
    - Nautical Research Center (Colin MacKenzie), 1996-1997; 27318; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Nautical Research Center (Colin MacKenzie))
    - Oral History Projects, 1991-1994; 27319; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Oral History Projects)
    - Paintings, 1984-1986; 6902; Stick, David, 1919-2009
      - Albums, 1985-1986; 27320; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Albums)
      - Appraisal (Barbara Schmidt), 1986; 27321; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Appraisal (Barbara Schmidt))
      - Beneficiaries of Trust, 1984; 27322; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Beneficiaries of Trust)
      - Donation Agreement (Cultural Resources), 1986; 27323; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Donation Agreement (Cultural Resources))
      - Lists to be Donated, circa 1986; 27324; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Lists to be Donated)
      - Planters Bank, 1985-1986; 27325; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Planters Bank)
    - Plans and Specifications, 1985-1987; 27326; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Plans and Specifications)
    - Plans for Library Addition, Elizabeth II Visitor's Center (Outer Banks History Center), 1987; 29321; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Plans for Library Addition, Elizabeth II Visitor's Center (Outer Banks History Center))
    - Prior Years, 1995-2001; 27327; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Prior Years)
    - Publications Committee, 1988-1997; 27328; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Publications Committee)
    - Roanoke Island Historical Association Collection in OBHC, Index to (Barbara Hird and lebame houston), circa 2000; 27329; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Roanoke Island Historical Association Collection in OBHC, Index to (Barbara Hird and lebame houston))